// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "Three year ago, ratio of Tom and Ram age’s was 5 : 6 respectively. After 12 years, this ratio becomes 6 : 7. How old is Ram at present?",
    answer: "93",
    options: ["87", "98", "93", "73"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "Ratio of ages of three girls are 5:8:10, six years ago, the sum of their ages was 28. Find their present ages.",
    answer: "10,16,20",
    options: ["10,16,20", "23,52,11", "75,86,13", "None"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "Shyam is younger than Sharuk by 22 years. If the ratio of their ages is 5:7, find the age of Shyam",
    answer: "55",
    options: ["100", "23", "55", "73"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "The ratio between the present ages of M and N is 8:9. If N is 6 years old than M, what will be the ratio of the ages of M and N after 6 years",
    answer: "Structured Query Language",
    options: ["9:10", "9:6", "9:11", "9:12"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "Ratio between vinodha and swetha is 7:6, After 8 Years vinodha’s age will be 29 years. What is swetha present age.",
    answer: "18",
    options: ["15", "12", "13", "18"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question:
      "In final exam of class IX there are 130 students 20 % students failed. How many students passed to class X?",
    answer: "104",
    options: ["105", "112", "104", "111"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "Sanjay gets 72 % marks in examinations. If these are 864 marks, find the maximum marks.",
    answer: "1200",
    options: ["1050", "860", "1200", "1300"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question:
      "In a college of 1335 students, 60 % are boys. Find the number of girls and number of boys in the college?",
    answer: "534,801",
    options: ["924,221", "691,404", "691,405", "534,801"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Find the increase value if 450 is increased by 90 %.",
    answer: "855",
    options: ["910", "855", "313", "545"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "The cost of a stencil is decreased by 30%. If the original cost is $140, find the decrease cost.",
    answer: "98",
    options: ["98", "100", "87", "101"],
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
];
